SAGAR PARMAR

UI/ UX DEVELOPER 👂 VADODARA, INDIA 📞 9714466108

° DETAILS °

Vadodara India 9714466108

sagarparmar881@gmail.com

° SKILLS °

C/C++

Python

Java

PHP

SQL

Git

HTML & CSS

JavaScript

jQuery

Adobe Photoshop

Adobe Illustrator

Adobe Premiere Pro

Adobe After Effects

Adobe XD

Figma

Corel Draw

Flutter

° LANGUAGES °

Gujarati

Hindi

English

PROFILE

Experienced UI/UX Developer with a demonstrated history of working in the information technology and services industry. Skilled in Mobile Application, Web Application, UI/UX, HTML/CSS/JS, Wordpress, Python, Graphics Design, Digital Marketer and Linux etc. strong engineering professional with a Bachelor of Technology (B. Tech) focused in Computer Science Engineering from Navrachana University.

EDUCATION

SSC, Kelavani English Medium School, Vadodara

June 2014 — March 2015

75.33

HSC, Vidhyut Board Vidhyalaya, Vadodara

June 2015 — March 2017

Bachelor, Navrachana University, Vadodara

June 2017 — June 2021

8.17

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Web Developer at Navrachana University, Vadodara

June 2021 — June 2021

SI Visa Consulting Pvt. Ltd. at Social Media Handler, Vadodara

September 2019 — September 2019

Balaji Rotomodulers at Graphics Designer, Vadodara

August 2019 — September 2019

Social Media Handler at Victory Education, Vadodara

February 2021

COURSES

Learn to Code with Python 3, Udemy

January 2020 — February 2020

Responsive Web Design, freeCodeCamp

January 2021 — March 2021

CERTIFICATIONS

Hack The Web Challenge, Developer Student Clubs

February 2020

Python, Silver Rank | HackerRank

March 2020

SQL, Silver Rank | HackerRank May 2020

* EXTRA-CURRICULAR ACTIVITIES

Web Developer at Navrachana University, Vadodara

A team of students from Computer Science Department of Navrachana University and Developer Students Club NUV were developing the official website under a long term plan for NUV to become #aatmanirbhar for tech support.

Online 3D Chess Game

August 2019 — May 2020

Developed a cross-platform, multiplayer game "Online 3D Chess Game" an android application which allows the users to play chess game over the internet. With additional features as animations, music, chat etc.

BharatMart App

August 2020 — May 2021

A complete E Commerce platform based on android and web was developed in this project. It was developed to connect local business owners and local customers. It is developed by keeping the vision of "Vocal for Local".

Graphics Designer at "The Dhaba"

June 2021

Designed a restaurant logo, business card and menu card design.

UI / UX Lead at Developer Student Clubs, Vadodara

September 2020 — June 2021

is INTERNSHIPS

Graphics Designer at SI Visa Consulting Pvt. Ltd., Vadodara

September 2019 — October 2019

Graphics Designer at Balaji Rotomoulders Pvt. Ltd.

September 2020 — June 2021

Social Media Handler at Victory Education

February 2021